Yarugaru Channel Yukariko
I'm in Gotemba today.
It's at night.
I forgot to take it.
I'm sorry.
I was just leaving.
Yes, sir.
I'll put a rubber band on.
Here you go, sir.
I'm going to eat now.
Dinner by yourself?
Yes, ramen.
Ramen again
You always eat ramen, don't you, Mr. Yamada?
That's right.
It's so fatty
More fatty
It's like pork bones
Oh, the soup is delicious
Wow, it's pork bone!
Gentle taste
Much better!
The other day, when my family and I went to a ramen restaurant, we talked...
I don't like natto in my ramen. I don't want nori in my ramen.
Do you understand? I understand that.
But I do want nori. Today...
We got together at 8:00 a.m. today.
But we didn't know if we had to book tickets in Japan.
We're taking the bus.
We checked the time and the place.
I didn't know that we had to get tickets or reserve seats.
And when I got there, it was like the bus was already full.
And I was like, "Oh my God, what am I going to do?
And then I saw someone else in the same situation.
They were tourists.
There was a couple.
I became friends with them.
I said, "Follow me, follow me, follow me.
I said, "Let's go together.
And they followed me.
We came to Gotemba together.
We finally got there and split up.
We were together for about 3 hours.
We were together the whole time.
He bought me nuggets and stuff.
I don't know if it was a thank you, but...
He said, "I'll buy you some nuggets!
He was like, "I'll buy it!
He said he'd buy it for us
So we gave him those Japanese sweets.
It took us less than an hour.
About 50 minutes.
We had about 50 minutes.
So I said, "Let's go kill some time.
It was like a Japanese supermarket.
Like a supermarket.
So I said, "Let's go.
I said let's go and we bought some stuff.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
It's like a Japanese supermarket.
Japanese sweets
I bought it!
Oops!
Ebisen (shrimp crackers)
Kappa Ebisen
You know what?
Later in the broadcast...
There were four of them.
That's right!
You're happy.
I'm glad.
I'd like to say that I had a wonderful encounter with you.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
Your face is a little green because of the reflection of the green color.
Mai.
What's that called?
The green one.
Mai.
Green bag.
Something like that.
Black roll
What do you mean by "black roll"?
CG or something like that
Green bag
Yes, yes, yes.
There are too many things
Goriba, Goriba, Goriba
Which one?
It's true, it's true, it's true...
Look
Look.
Wait, Vivian!
Vivian!
Vivian, let's see!
I'll take a peek
The tapioca!
You found it!
Yes, I don't know why I'm here.
If you find it, it's not going to be a cash register.
Yeah, when I realized that.
It looked like I should buy it.
So I did.
Tapioca is booming.
We are.
Yes, we are.
Let's see...
I'm Black Mine Kitty.
So...
Continue shopping
I'm going to have fun!
I bought 3 pairs of shoes!
Finally.
What time did you do this?
I just decided to go in.
And I bought a lot of shoes there.
I bought two pairs.
They were so cute.
They were so cute!
The clerk was so kind.
She was like, "How about these? like, "How about this one?
She was very cooperative.
They gave me a lot of suggestions.
All of them.
It's really a lot of people.
Not just one.
Yes, it's not just the two of us.
Everyone was so nice to me.
It was fun!
And that's why
I can't introduce you.
I don't have a place for it.
on social networking sites.
I thought you were wearing new shoes.
That's what I mean.
You commented to me that you bought these.
on social media
Bye-bye bread
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye.
You don't have to look at Rayber.
Sunglasses.
Look at my sunglasses.
Um...
I have to wait for the bus.
Thank you very much.
I'm practicing today.
Till bus time.
Charcoal rice.
What's with the crunchy ramen noodles?
No, it's not ramen.
It's soup.
Oh no, Chinese food for lunch again!
I want to eat it soooooooooooooooo fast!
I didn't have much time.
Yeah, you eat really fast.
Really?
I eat really fast.
I had a lot of trouble with my mouth.
Oh, yeah? Really?
It must have been about an hour.
Yamamoto-san's pointing out zulz when we were eating ramen noodles.
I thought it was a good idea.
I knew I liked the big black one.
It's refreshing to get away from it all.
The nature was amazing, the air was so nice.
I want to go to a different place next time.
I'll go next time. I'm sure you'll meet some nice people.
I'm telling the truth. I met a nice Torii-san.
I was happy. As a boy of your age...
As a boy of your age, I was happy to meet a nice Torii-san.
But I thought, "I don't recognize him.
But another girl approached me.
I'm rooting for you. I'm so happy.
I was so surprised. She came to me like a toddler.
I was so happy.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. If you're here.
Thank you.
I hope you're doing well.
I wish you a safe trip home.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
I'll be back with something to do.
I'll be in Cute Community
It's an off day.
It's a day.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching.